let cssquestions = {
    time: 18, //in min
    questions: [
        {
            question: "1. CSS means?",
            option1: "Code Style Sheets",
            option2: "Cardcasting Style Sheets",
            option3: "Corcading Style Sheets",
            option4: "Cascading Style Sheets",
            correctresponse: "Cascading Style Sheets",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "2. What does CSS stand for?",
            option1: "Creative Style Sheets",
            option2: "Cascading Style Sheets",
            option3: "Computer Style Sheets",
            option4: "Colorful Style Sheets",
            correctresponse: "Cascading Style Sheets",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "3. Which HTML tag is used to define an internal CSS?",
            option1: "<style>",
            option2: "<script>",
            option3: "<css>",
            option4: "<link>",
            correctresponse: "<style>",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "4. Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
            option1: "font",
            option2: "styles",
            option3: "class",
            option4: "style",
            correctresponse: "style",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "5. How do you select elements with the class name 'test'?",
            option1: "#test",
            option2: ".test",
            option3: "test",
            option4: "*test",
            correctresponse: ".test",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "6. Which property is used to change the background color?",
            option1: "color",
            option2: "bgcolor",
            option3: "background-color",
            option4: "background",
            correctresponse: "background-color",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "7. Which CSS property controls text size?",
            option1: "text-style",
            option2: "font-style",
            option3: "font-size",
            option4: "text-size",
            correctresponse: "font-size",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "8. How do you make the text bold in CSS?",
            option1: "font-weight: bold;",
            option2: "text-weight: bold;",
            option3: "font-style: bold;",
            option4: "text-style: bold;",
            correctresponse: "font-weight: bold;",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "9. How do you add a comment in CSS?",
            option1: "// this is a comment",
            option2: "/* this is a comment */",
            option3: "<!-- this is a comment -->",
            option4: "' this is a comment",
            correctresponse: "/* this is a comment */",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "10. How do you make a list that lists items with square bullets?",
            option1: "list-style-type: square;",
            option2: "list-style-type: circle;",
            option3: "list-style-type: disc;",
            option4: "list-style-type: bullet;",
            correctresponse: "list-style-type: square;",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "11. How do you select elements with the ID 'demo'?",
            option1: "#demo",
            option2: ".demo",
            option3: "demo",
            option4: "id-demo",
            correctresponse: "#demo",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "12. What is the default value of the 'position' property?",
            option1: "absolute",
            option2: "relative",
            option3: "static",
            option4: "fixed",
            correctresponse: "static",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "13. Which property is used to set the spacing between lines of text?",
            option1: "letter-spacing",
            option2: "line-spacing",
            option3: "line-height",
            option4: "text-spacing",
            correctresponse: "line-height",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "14. Which CSS property controls the visibility of an element?",
            option1: "display",
            option2: "visibility",
            option3: "opacity",
            option4: "hidden",
            correctresponse: "visibility",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "15. How do you change the text color of an element in CSS?",
            option1: "text-color",
            option2: "color",
            option3: "font-color",
            option4: "style-color",
            correctresponse: "color",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "16. Which property is used to change the left margin of an element?",
            option1: "margin-left",
            option2: "margin-right",
            option3: "padding-left",
            option4: "padding-right",
            correctresponse: "margin-left",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "17. How do you make a website responsive in CSS?",
            option1: "Use @responsive",
            option2: "Use @media queries",
            option3: "Use @flexible",
            option4: "Use @viewport",
            correctresponse: "Use @media queries",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "18. Which property is used to align text to the center?",
            option1: "text-align: center;",
            option2: "align: center;",
            option3: "vertical-align: center;",
            option4: "text-position: center;",
            correctresponse: "text-align: center;",
            time: 1,
        },

        // Add more if needed.
    ],
};

export default cssquestions;
